<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Peekaboo World</title>
    <link>https://peekaboo.travel/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Peekaboo World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://peekaboo.travel/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel by Plane, Bus, or Train: Packing Tips for Travel with Preschoolers</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/travel-by-plane-bus-or-train-packing-tips-for-travel-with-preschoolers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/travel-by-plane-bus-or-train-packing-tips-for-travel-with-preschoolers/</guid>
      <description>Our kids have been pretty impressive little travelers on our adventures so far. From 15+ hour plane trips, 2 hour bus rides, or the day to day commute, I have gained some mommy wisdom on how to keep the kids entertained and avoid overpacking when on the go. The &amp;ldquo;less is more&amp;rdquo; mantra is surprisingly relevant when it comes to travelling with children.
We take public transportation on a daily basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollókő, Hungary</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/holl%C3%B3k%C5%91-hungary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/holl%C3%B3k%C5%91-hungary/</guid>
      <description>Step back in time and enjoy a day trip to this authentic Hungarian village located in the hills 100km northeast of Budapest. A hidden gem and UNESCO World Heritage Site, Hollókő is a Palóc ethnographic village. It is considered a &amp;ldquo;living village&amp;rdquo;, as people continue to inhabit the village, preserving Palóc traditions and heritage.
Hollókő&amp;rsquo;s history dates back to the 13th century with the original construction of its castle, which was intended to protect the region from additional Mongol invasions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Szeged, Hungary</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/szeged-hungary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/szeged-hungary/</guid>
      <description>We had such a delightful time visiting old friends in Szeged. Nothing beats a personal tour by a local, particularly one flexible enough to detour to the playground. It was so refreshing not to rely on google maps, wikipedia, and the like to see the &amp;ldquo;top sights&amp;rdquo; and navigate a new city. We also learned so much more about the history of the city in such a short time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cassis and the Calanques National Park, France</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/cassis-and-the-calanques-national-park-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/cassis-and-the-calanques-national-park-france/</guid>
      <description>Cassis is a picturesque fishing town just 20km east of Marseille. The harbour is filled with sailboats and lined by colorful cafes and shops. An old chateau sits atop the rocky cliffs overlooking the city. It is a quaint, peaceful setting with magnificent views of the Mediterranean coastline. We walked through the harbour to begin our trek to the Calanques and returned to Cassis in the afternoon to enjoy a well-deserved al fresco meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marseille, France</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/marseille-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/marseille-france/</guid>
      <description>We took a speed train from Lyon to Marseille and stayed two nights in this eclectic port city. Marseille is located on the Mediterranean coast and has played a central role in trade since its origination in 600 B.C. It is a lively multicultural city with north African and Islamic influences. We stayed in the Old Port (Vieux Port), which is bustling with cafes and pubs late into the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyon, France</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/lyon-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/lyon-france/</guid>
      <description>We had the pleasure of visiting Lyon on our World Cup trip to France. Lyon is a very welcoming city with lovely French charm. Although it ranks as the third largest city in France, we enjoyed the more leisurely pace and friendliness of the Lyonnaise people. As the culinary capitol of France, we were delighted by the cuisine. From the buttery croissants at the boulangerie on the corner to an elegant three course meal in the historic Port Vieux, it is fair to say that we ate our way through the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Cup Champs</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/world-cup-champs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/world-cup-champs/</guid>
      <description>Gabe and I were fortunate enough to go on our first big kid-free getaway in France shortly after our arrival in Europe. Our main draw was watching the FIFA Women&amp;rsquo;s World Cup and seriously, what better place than France? We bought our tickets for the semi-finals and final match in Lyon prior to the group announcements and were just banking on the USA making it through. It was a tough road at times, as the US faced off against the host nation of France and a highly competitive English squad prior to meeting the Netherlands in the finals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Minutia</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/the-minutia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/the-minutia/</guid>
      <description>How do you pack up and move abroad for a year? On the stateside, we rented our home, moved all of our belongings to a storage unit, found temporary “housing” for our pup, sold a car, and left a job. Gabe will continue to work as a software engineer. I will be happily unemployed and preoccupied with learning the ropes of our new city. Once the kids start school I will be enrolling in language classes and enjoying some free time to re-balance life as a mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Our Feet Wet</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/getting-our-feet-wet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/getting-our-feet-wet/</guid>
      <description>I had planned on getting started on my blog much sooner, but as it turns out, moving abroad and venturing between 4 countries in the first 3 weeks is quite a lot to navigate! We have a beautiful apartment in Budapest, which we have spent very little time in thus far. We are finally heading back to settle in and unpack!
So what have we been up to?
We spent the first two weeks traveling back and forth between Budapest and Gabe’s hometown of Fülek, Slovakia, which is 2 hours straight north from Budapest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>