<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hungary on Peekaboo World</title>
    <link>https://peekaboo.travel/countries/hungary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hungary on Peekaboo World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://peekaboo.travel/countries/hungary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Charming Day Trip to Szentendre</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/a-charming-day-trip-to-szentendre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/a-charming-day-trip-to-szentendre/</guid>
      <description>Szentendre is a small artsy town in an idyllic setting on the Danube just north of Budapest. It is known for its cafes, museums, churches, and galleries. Its proximity to Budapest and undeniable charm make it a very popular day trip destination.
Szentendre’s baroque architecture and mediterranean feel stem from its multicultural past. This riverside city has been settled in some form since ancient times and throughout its history has acted as a haven for refugees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical tips for travel in Budapest</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/practical-tips-for-travel-in-budapest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/practical-tips-for-travel-in-budapest/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to take a moment to share our top tips for traveling in and around Budapest with kids. We learned very quickly through our own adventures (and misadventures) that you have to be a little more prepared on an everyday basis when navigating Budapest. You don’t necessarily need to carry a Mary Poppins bag, but taking a few extra steps can help make your travels go more smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budapest: Top 6 family excursions WITH playgrounds</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/family-playgrounds-excursions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/family-playgrounds-excursions/</guid>
      <description>One of the tricky parts about traveling with children is finding balance. You want to see the sights, but little legs and limited attention spans sometimes put a wrench in your plans. When we travel we strive to combine play with sightseeing. Carving out time for the kids to run free allows them to recharge and makes sight-seeing more exciting for everyone. Fortunately, Budapest has a plethora of unique playgrounds to accomplish just that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Győr, Hungary</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/gyor-hungary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/gyor-hungary/</guid>
      <description>We went by train to Győr this past weekend and were pleasantly surprised by the city’s charm. Located within the “golden triangle” of Budapest, Vienna, and Bratislava, the city of Győr is a perfect destination for a day trip or weekend getaway.
We arrived in Győr with no itinerary or agenda and enjoyed strolling through the old town at a leisurely pace. The city is very walkable, even for little legs, as most of the main sites are within the city centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollókő, Hungary</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/holloko-hungary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/holloko-hungary/</guid>
      <description>Step back in time and enjoy a day trip to this authentic Hungarian village located in the hills 100km northeast of Budapest. A hidden gem and UNESCO World Heritage Site, Hollókő is a Palóc ethnographic village. It is considered a &amp;ldquo;living village&amp;rdquo;, as people continue to inhabit the village, preserving Palóc traditions and heritage.
Hollókő&amp;rsquo;s history dates back to the 13th century with the original construction of its castle, which was intended to protect the region from additional Mongol invasions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Szeged, Hungary</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/szeged-hungary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/szeged-hungary/</guid>
      <description>We had such a delightful time visiting old friends in Szeged. Nothing beats a personal tour by a local, particularly one flexible enough to detour to the playground. It was so refreshing not to rely on google maps, wikipedia, and the like to see the &amp;ldquo;top sights&amp;rdquo; and navigate a new city. We also learned so much more about the history of the city in such a short time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Minutia</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/minutia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/minutia/</guid>
      <description>How do you pack up and move abroad for a year? On the stateside, we rented our home, moved all of our belongings to a storage unit, found temporary “housing” for our pup, sold a car, and left a job. Gabe will continue to work as a software engineer. I will be happily unemployed and preoccupied with learning the ropes of our new city. Once the kids start school I will be enrolling in language classes and enjoying some free time to re-balance life as a mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Our Feet Wet</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/wet-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/wet-feet/</guid>
      <description>I had planned on getting started on my blog much sooner, but as it turns out, moving abroad and venturing between 4 countries in the first 3 weeks is quite a lot to navigate! We have a beautiful apartment in Budapest, which we have spent very little time in thus far. We are finally heading back to settle in and unpack!
So what have we been up to?
We spent the first two weeks traveling back and forth between Budapest and Gabe’s hometown of Fülek, Slovakia, which is 2 hours straight north from Budapest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>