<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portugal on Peekaboo World</title>
    <link>https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/countries/portugal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portugal on Peekaboo World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/countries/portugal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seaside Escape to Cascais Portugal</title>
      <link>https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/seaside-escape-to-cascais-portugal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/seaside-escape-to-cascais-portugal/</guid>
      <description>Cascais is a quaint seaside town and historic fishing village located on the Portuguese Riviera. An easy day trip from Lisbon, Cascais is known for its dramatic rocky coastline, old world charm, and perfectly relaxed pace. Our visit to Cascais was one of the highlights of our trip to Portugal, as the beach is always calling our children’s names.
Although its history dates back to ancient times, Cascais first began to flourish in the 12th and 13th centuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Magical Day in Sintra with Kids</title>
      <link>https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/a-magical-day-in-sintra-with-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/a-magical-day-in-sintra-with-kids/</guid>
      <description>Sintra is a magical oasis set in the mountains just a short train ride from Lisbon. With a slew of historic palaces and castles, whimsical gardens, and winding cobblestone streets, a visit to Sintra is like stepping into a fairytale. The city of Sintra is classified as a UNESCO World Heritage site and is the most popular day trip from Lisbon. We were limited to one day exploring this special place, but I would strongly advise at least two days to better enjoy all that Sintra has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Explorers in Lisbon: A Four Day Family Itinerary</title>
      <link>https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/little-explorers-in-lisbon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gcziprusz.github.io/peekaboo.travel/little-explorers-in-lisbon/</guid>
      <description>Lisbon is one of the oldest cities in the world, full of magnificent history, culture, and charm. From its iconic azulejos tiles and sweeping views to its historical sites and delicious cuisine, Lisbon is a destination that the whole family can enjoy.
Lisbon offers a great opportunity for global learning. All kids love adventures. Introduce a few of the famous Portueguese explorers from the Age of Discovery and talk about their voyages as you stroll Lisbon&amp;rsquo;s marinas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>