<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peekaboo World</title>
    <link>https://peekaboo.travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Peekaboo World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://peekaboo.travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cassis and the Calanques National Park, France</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/cassis-and-the-calanques-national-park-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/cassis-and-the-calanques-national-park-france/</guid>
      <description>Cassis
is a picturesque fishing town just 20km east of Marseille. The harbour is filled with sailboats and lined by colorful cafes and shops. An old chateau sits atop the rocky cliffs overlooking the city. It is a quaint, peaceful setting with magnificent views of the Mediterranean coastline. We walked through the harbour to begin our trek to the Calanques and returned to Cassis in the afternoon to enjoy a well-deserved al fresco meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marseille, France</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/marseille-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/marseille-france/</guid>
      <description>We took a speed train from Lyon to Marseille and stayed two nights in this eclectic port city. Marseille is located on the Mediterranean coast and has played a central role in trade since its origination in 600 B.C. It is a lively multicultural city with north African and Islamic influences. We stayed in the Old Port (Vieux Port), which is bustling with cafes and pubs late into the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyon, France</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/lyon-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/lyon-france/</guid>
      <description>We had the pleasure of visiting Lyon on our World Cup trip to France. Lyon is a very welcoming city with lovely French charm. Although it ranks as the third largest city in France, we enjoyed the more leisurely pace and friendliness of the Lyonnaise people. As the culinary capitol of France, we were delighted by the cuisine. From the buttery croissants at the boulangerie on the corner to an elegant three course meal in the historic Port Vieux, it is fair to say that we ate our way through the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Cup Champs</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/world-cup-champs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/world-cup-champs/</guid>
      <description>Gabe and I were fortunate enough to go on our first big kid-free getaway in France shortly after our arrival in Europe. Our main draw was watching the FIFA Women&amp;rsquo;s World Cup and seriously, what better place than France? We bought our tickets for the semi-finals and final match in Lyon prior to the group announcements and were just banking on the USA making it through. It was a tough road at times, as the US faced off against the host nation of France and a highly competitive English squad prior to meeting the Netherlands in the finals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Minutia</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/the-minutia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/the-minutia/</guid>
      <description>How do you pack up and move abroad for a year? On the stateside, we rented our home, moved all of our belongings to a storage unit, found temporary “housing” for our pup, sold a car, and left a job. Gabe will continue to work as a software engineer. I will be happily unemployed and preoccupied with learning the ropes of our new city. Once the kids start school I will be enrolling in language classes and enjoying some free time to re-balance life as a mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Our Feet Wet</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/getting-our-feet-wet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/getting-our-feet-wet/</guid>
      <description>I had planned on getting started on my blog much sooner, but as it turns out, moving abroad and venturing between 4 countries in the first 3 weeks is quite a lot to navigate! We have a beautiful apartment in Budapest, which we have spent very little time in thus far. We are finally heading back to settle in and unpack!
So what have we been up to?
We spent the first two weeks traveling back and forth between Budapest and Gabe’s hometown of Fülek, Slovakia, which is 2 hours straight north from Budapest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://peekaboo.travel/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 11:02:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peekaboo.travel/about/</guid>
      <description>We are excited to embark on our big adventure, moving from Nashville, Tennessee to Budapest, Hungary. The vibrant city of Budapest will be our home base and from there we plan to travel throughout Europe to destinations both big and small. It will be a year of excitement, challenges, growth, and reflection. By sharing our stories we hope to inspire global curiosity and to encourage other families to seek out adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>